Map ques = {
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "hololive",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is yagoo real name?",
      "correct_answer": "Motoaki Tanigo",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Yagoo is Yagoo", "Motoaki seki", "Kazuyuki Fukuda"]
    },
    {
      "category": "hololive",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "As of 2021, how many active Vtuber are manages by Hololive?",
      "correct_answer": "52",
      "incorrect_answers": ["46", "50", "56"]
    },
    {
      "category": "hololive",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who comes with the name yagoo?",
      "correct_answer": "subaru",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Pekora", "Marine", "Haachama"]
    },
    {
      "category": "hololive",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Akai Haato is also known as",
      "correct_answer": "Haachama",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Pekora", "subaru", "Amane Kanata"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "On which date our smol shark hits 1m subscriber?",
      "correct_answer": "22 Oct",
      "incorrect_answers": ["5 Nov", "25 Dec", "26 Nov"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who Quotes this " "You can't be mad at me... I'm cute!" " ",
      "correct_answer": "gura",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Anya", "Amelia", "Kiara"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Gura comes from _______?",
      "correct_answer": "Atlantis",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sea", "Pond", "Underworld"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "what kind of shark  gawr gura is according to her?",
      "correct_answer": "gura shark",
      "incorrect_answers": ["salmon shark", "smol shark", "baby shark"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is height of gura in cm?",
      "correct_answer": "141",
      "incorrect_answers": ["140", "145", "138"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is name of gura mascot?",
      "correct_answer": "Bloop",
      "incorrect_answers": ["emergency food", "Chumbuds", "NOAA"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Are you a _____?",
      "correct_answer": "Shrimp",
      "incorrect_answers": ["simp"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Gura birthdate?(anniversary of her arrival on land)",
      "correct_answer": "20 june",
      "incorrect_answers": ["20 july", "25 august", "25 december"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Is gura is Shortest member of hololive",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What gura biggest fear?",
      "correct_answer": "loud stomak",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "hot sand",
        "Swiming without floaties",
        "eating bloop"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is gura age",
      "correct_answer": "It's over 9,000!",
      "incorrect_answers": ["9,361", "9,927", "9,492"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the memeber is hydrodynamic",
      "correct_answer": "gura",
      "incorrect_answers": ["watson", "kiara", "Korone"]
    },
    {
      "category": "gura",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Its ____",
      "correct_answer": "a!",
      "incorrect_answers": ["ahh!", "A!", "aa!"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pekora",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What generation is Usada Pekora ~peko",
      "correct_answer": "third",
      "incorrect_answers": ["first", "second", "fifth"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pekora",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "which option represent Pekora laugh ~peko",
      "correct_answer": "AH↓ HA↑ HA↑ HA↑",
      "incorrect_answers": ["hahaha", "HA↑ HA↑ HA↑", "lol"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pekora",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "when pekora debuted on YouTube with her introductory stream",
      "correct_answer": "17 July",
      "incorrect_answers": ["28 May", "7 July ", "13 June"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pekora",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "Pekora is _______ memeber of hololive to reach 1 million YouTube subscribers",
      "correct_answer": "fourth",
      "incorrect_answers": ["second", "third", "Sixth"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pekora",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Pekora's scarf is actually her pet named _____",
      "correct_answer": "Don-chan",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Nousagi", "Usada-chan", "cho-chan"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pekora",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "Usada Kensetsu (Pekora company on the hololive Minecraft JP server) first employee was ______.",
      "correct_answer": "Moona Hoshinova",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Amane Kanata", "Uruha Rushia", "Shirogane Noel"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pekora",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "according to Pekora, bunny girls don't wear panties",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Korone",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "If Human is turtle, Turtle is human,Turtle is korone,Korone is human,Human is doggo,Doggo is ______",
      "correct_answer": "human",
      "incorrect_answers": ["korone", "doggo", "turtle"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Korone",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "Korone favorite demon in doom, hint :Bethesda-san even give her stuff toy of that demon",
      "correct_answer": "Cacodemon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Malwrath", "Wretched", "Pinky"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Korone",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which game reference Korone in their easter egg",
      "correct_answer": "Doom Eternal",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Crash Bandicoot 4",
        "Hidden Folks",
        "Banjo-kazooie"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Korone",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "Inugami Korone is the _______ hololive VTuber to reach 1 million subscribers",
      "correct_answer": "second",
      "incorrect_answers": ["fourth", "third", "Sixth"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Marine",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "Marine reached 1,000,000 subscribers on YouTube, making her the _____ hololive member and the _____ member of the Japanese branch",
      "correct_answer": "6th,5th",
      "incorrect_answers": ["5th,3rd", "8th,5th", "7th,4th"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Marine",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Marine allergic to",
      "correct_answer": "Cats",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Dogs", "Fish", "salt"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Amelia",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "Did Amelia reach 1m subscribers?,making her the 9th hololive member",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Amelia",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Name of Amelia mascot is",
      "correct_answer": "Bubba",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Bobbo", "doggo", "tea"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Amelia",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question":
          "Did Amelia reach 1m subscribers?,making her the 9th hololive member",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Amelia",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Amelia birth date",
      "correct_answer": "6 January",
      "incorrect_answers": ["15 January", "6 June", "15 June"]
    },
  ]
};
